We want to share with you the production techniques of the plate buckle
This time, the performance of the plate buckle is mainly performed in the form of sewing and folding
Then let's make a curved board
Set its width and height
18 and 2 respectively
Next, let's choose its edge line
Then select
Create an internal line between the lines
Set three internal lines here
In order to make it more obvious in the 3D window
Set a background color for it
Next, we use the 3D model to create a 3D model
Use the folding arrangement tool
Fold the three internal lines one by one
Fold it into such a square
Next, let's copy a few
We switch to the perspective of positive 2
We can choose this square
We can copy a few out
Copy one out
We rotate it
When rotating
You can hold down the Shift key
Make a 90-degree rotation
After rotating
Move to adjust the position
When adjusting
You need to pay attention to its position
Two are outside
Two are inside
Then we can temporarily not adjust it now
Let's copy one out
Then we put it on top
We also rotate it
Rotate it again
Make it so it's not on the same position
And then adjust the position
Now we can adjust the position
Then here
We use the folding arrangement
To show a palm buckle like this
Next
We just need adjust its position
The two opposite sides are outside
Two opposites are inside
First of all
Let's take a look at the version first
For example, two of them are inside, and these two need to be outside.
For example, this side of it and the other side of it are inside, right?
Then you need to drag this side out for it.
After dragging this side out, let's select it first.
There is such a blue dot. Let's move it.
We need to drag this side out.
Here you can use the selection grid tool to select it.
You can see that because this version is relatively small,
its particle diameter is a default of 20.
So when you select it, it will come out a little more.
So here you first reduce its particle diameter to 1.
Then adjust the conflict thickness to 1.5.
Next, let's make a choice.
You can see that it can make a good choice.
After selecting, we can move it.
Let's see if its opposite side is also outside.
Next, the same.
Let's take a look at this side.
It is outside.
Then this side also needs to be outside.
Then we can do this.
You can make a little choice like this.
For example, we can select this frame.
Then pull it out.
Let's take a look at this side again.
This side is already done.
Two sides are outside.
Two sides are inside.
Then let's take a look at this side again.
Two sides are outside.
Two sides are inside.
Let's take a look at this side again.
It is not inside.
You need to adjust it.
Make a choice.
Move this side out.
Let's take a look at this side again.
Then this is the way of folding arrangement.
To show the buckled head.
Finally, check again.
Two are outside.
Two are inside.
Then this is also two outside.
And these two are outside.
Two are inside.
After all this is done.
Here is a tip for you.
After choosing.
If you accidentally can't see it.
Then you can click the F key.
You can focus on the version you choose.
Next, we use the sewing tool to sew it.
After sewing, turn on the simulation.
Simulate.
Because it is in the air.
So it will fall down.
Now.
There is probably such a buckled head effect.
Next.
We need to make it more detailed.
First.
You need to use this edit version tool.
Delete its internal line.
In the real situation.
It is a relatively smooth effect.
There is no fold.
Here you need to delete it.
Second.
You can take a look.
Now it is the texture surface.
Change to dense texture surface display.
Take a look at the effect.
There is a little gap in the middle.
You can adjust the conflict thickness.
Adjust to 1.
The particles are confined here.
According to your computer performance.
Set.
Here it is reduced to 0.8.
Set a little bit of rendering thickness.
The rendering thickness is set to 0.5.
You can take a look.
There is such an effect.
Next.
We still need to make the following two ropes.
It is the two roots below the buckled head.
A rope down.
Need to draw a board.
We can freeze it first.
Then the buckled head.
Move to the air.
There is still a little gap here.
Need to adjust the shape again.
Check if there is still a gap.
After the production is done.
You can adjust the shape.
Here you can.
Shorten its length a little bit.
Simulate.
Adjust the position.
Then.
Perform the same operation.
This is temporarily.
Do not adjust first.
Wait a minute.
Need to put these two ropes.
Put in the middle of this.
Choose these two boards.
Perform a freeze.
For simulation.
Then.
We first.
Pull it up a little bit.
Simulate it.
Then.
Pull it down a little bit.
There is a little gap in the middle.
Press the W key.
You can add a fixed pin.
For example.
You can add a fixed pin here.
After pulling it to such a degree.
This.
You can take a look.
It still has a little gap now.
You can also put it.
Tighten it a little bit.
Look at its conflict thickness.
Set to 0.5.
Then.
We just.
This.
Give it to sew on this.
Here.
Add a internal thread to it.
For example.
At this position.
We give it to him.
Add an internal thread first.
To him.
Perform a seam.
First,
it is disengaged.
Then.
We have a line.
Then move to the sewing box
You can use the positioning tool
And press the F key to locate
First freeze
Give it a position
And press the F key to locate
Change it to texture surface
Let's see the sewing box
Need to sew again
Now the sewing line direction is reversed
Give it a change of the direction of the sewing line
Give it a position adjustment
This length, you can make it a little longer
We give it again
Copy another one
There will be an internal line here
Sew it for it
This length
You can adjust it according to the actual
You can see
Because these two panels
Is a newly designed panel
So its particle diameter is relatively large
So you can adjust it to 1
The conflict thickness is also adjusted to 1
Next, adjust to 0.5
Feel this sewing line
It's a little bit reversed
Let's take a look
You have to adjust it a little bit
You can press the W key
Add a fixed needle to it
Set it aside
Here is the same
Add a fixed needle
Press the W key in the simulated state
You can give it a position adjustment
Here, we will adjust it again roughly
You can do this
Change to dense texture display
Here
We can adjust its particle diameter
You can reduce it a little bit
Reduce to 0.8
In fact
Its width is not so wide
Here
You can adjust it to a state of 1
This side can probably be adjusted to 1
Here, the same operation is carried out
You can set it according to the actual situation
The actual plate buckle
The part of the rope down
Is made of two layers
So
If you want to be more realistic
We can do it with the class layer
Let's simulate it
In the simulation process
You can delete a fixed needle
It can be shown
The shape of the fixed needle is not very natural
Because of this fixed needle
The shape is not very natural
Adjust the shape
And its sewing line part
Because of its real effect
It is folded over
So you are here
You can put its sewing line strength
Adjust to 0
Or delete the line drawing
Just do it
Now apply a fabric to it
Use the sewing fabric
Or the fabric of the hem
For example
What is applied here is the sewing fabric
It is relatively thin
This fabric is set to transparency
Adjust it back
The opacity is set to 0
Simulate it again
for stretching
Take a look at its effect
For stretching
Set a color for it
Set the stretching dimension
It has this kind of trace
In fact, there is no trace
So when we are doing it here
We also need this trace
Remove it like this
Just change its intensity to 0
Let's take a look at the effect
Finally adjust the position and shape
Then our plate buckle is ready